Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Diana Dolev on Israeli Government Raids on 4/26 and Violent Police Response at 4/30 Demonstration; Michael Ratner on Torture Memos and Obama Responses; Esther Kaplan and Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark on Senator Arlen Specter Defection; Part 1 of Steve Zeitlin Talk on Jewish Humor, 2009-05-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_321)
- Michael Ratner Torture Memos, 2009-05-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_297)
- Music Special Hosted by Abe Velez with Basya Schechter, Roberto Rodriguez, and Sarah Aroeste, 2009-05-10 (Box 20, Item 718_0871)
- Marathon Music Special: Abe Velez with Basya Schechter on Her Band, Part 1, 2009-05-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_323)
- Marathon Music Special: Abe Velez with Roberto Rodriguez and Sarah Aroeste, Part 2, 2009-05-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_324)
- Sarah Ludwig on Credit Card Reform Legislation; Abe Velez on Hip Hop Hoodio's New CD, Carne Masada; Jeff Sharlet on Fundamentalists in Military, 2009-05-31 (Box 20, Item 718_0888)
- Sarah Ludwig on Credit Card Reform Legislation; Abe Velez and Josh Norek on Carne Masada; Jeff Sharlet on His Article, "Jesus Killed Mohammed," and Fundamentalists in the Military, 2009-05-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_325)
- Kiera Feldman with Felice Gelman on Gaza Delegation; Dan Fleshler on Transforming America's Israel Lobby; Jeremy Gillick on Article, "The Coming of the Intermarried Rabbi", 2009-06-07 (Box 20, Item 718_0889)
- Kiera Feldman with Felice Gelman on Gaza Delegation; Dan Fleshler on Transforming America's Israel Lobby; Jeremy Gillick on Article, "The Coming of the Intermarried Rabbi", 2009-06-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_327)
- Abe Velez with Frank London, 2009-06-14 (Box 20, Item 718_0892)
- Abe Velez with Frank London, 2009-06-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_328)
- Nathaniel Popper on Congress Hotel Strike in Chicago; Leonard Zeskind on Book,Blood and Politics and White Supremacy; Naftaly Gliksberg on Look Into My Eyes, 2009-06-21 (Box 20, Item 718_0867)
- Nathaniel Popper on Congress Hotel Strike in Chicago; Leonard Zeskind on White Supremacy and His Book, Blood and Politics; Naftaly Gliksberg on Look Into My Eyes, 2009-06-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_329)
- Gay Pride: Alisa Solomon with Haneen Maikey, Richard Kim, and Tim McCaskell, 2009-06-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_296)
- Tom Robbins on State Senate Meltdown; Roya Hakakian on Iranian Elections; Ewa Jasiewicz on Boat Interdiction, 2009-07-05 (Box 20, Item 718_0875)
- Tom Robbins State Senate - What's at Stake?; Roya Hakakian on Iran; Ewa Jasiewicz of Free Gaza Movement, 2009-07-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_331)
- Max Fraser Interviews Beryl Satter on Family Properties: Race, Real Estate, and the Exploitation of Black Urban America, 2009-07-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_353)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on Health Care Reform; Geoffrey Aronson on Diplomatic Efforts to Freeze Settlements; Aviva Kempner, Director of Yoo-Hoo, Mrs. Goldberg, 2009-07-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_330)
- Alisa Solomon with Yael Bartana on Exhibition; Lev Dodin on Life and Fate; Mark Laiosa with Lev Raphael on My Germany, 2009-07-19 (Box 20, Item 718_0895)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Yael Bartana, 2009-07-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_298)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Israeli Artist Yael Bartana; Lev Dodin on Life and Fate at Lincoln Center Festival; Mark Laiosa interviews Lev Raphael on My Germany, 2009-07-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_332)
- Alisa Solomon, Haneen Maikey, and Richard Kim on Israel's Branding Campaign Targeting LGBTQ Communities; Beryl Satter on Book Family Properties, 2009-07-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_333)
- Adina Hoffman on My Happiness Bears No Relation to Happiness: A Poet's Life in the Palestinian Century, 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_310)
- Taha Muhammad Ali with Peter Cole, Readings: "Revenge" and "Abd el-Hadi Fights a Superpower", 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_357)
- Taha Muhammad Ali with Peter Cole, Readings, 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_358)
- Rachel Tzvia Back on With an Iron Pen: Twenty Years of Hebrew Protest Poetry, 2009-08-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_335)
- Mazel Tov Mis Amigos with Abe Velez, 2009-08-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_336)
- Neve Gordon on Israel Boycott; Daniel Levy about the Israel Project; Esther Broner on The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box 20, Item 718_0877)
- Josh Nathan-Kazis with Daniel Levy on The Israel Project, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_279)
- Esther Broner on The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_280)
- Neve Gordon on BDS Movement; Josh Nathan-Kazis Talks with Daniel Leux about The Israel Project; Esther Broner on Her Book The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_337)
- Esther Broner on Her Book The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_352)
- Kiera Feldman Reports on Jews for Jesus Campaign, 2009-09-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_302)
- Timothy Snyder on Holocaust: The Ignored Reality; Mandy Katz on Branding Israel; Jews for Jesus, 36th Annual Summer Witnessing Campaign, 2009-09-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_339)
- Abe Velez Music, 2009-09-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_338)
- Co-host Kiera Feldman with Rabbi Arthur Waskow on Conference of Presidents and Goldstone Gaza Report; Mandy Katz on Israel's Branding Campaign; Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box 20, Item 718_0866)
- Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_282)
- Rabbi Arthur Waskow, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_301)
- Arthur Waskow on Iran; Goldstone Gaza Report; Mandy Katz on Israel Branding; Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_340)
- Emily Seif Reporting on Westboro Baptist Church, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_284)
- A Report from Westboro Baptist Church Protests at Brooklyn Synagogues; Phyllis Bennis, Rashid Khalidi, and Avi Shlaim on Goldstone Report; Jeffrey Shandler on Jews, God, and Videotape, 2009-09-27 (Box 20, Item 718_0865)
- Alisa Solomon with Jeffrey Shandler, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_300)
- A Report from Westboro Baptist Church Anti-Jew, Anti-Gay Protests at Brooklyn Synagogues; Phyllis Bennis, Rashid Khalidi, and Avi Shlaim on Freeze and Goldstone Report; Alisa Solomon Talks with Jeff Shandler on Khazans, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_341)
- Cantors: Kol Nidre (Rosenblatt, Oysler, Tucker), Avinu Malkeinu (Jennie Goldstein, B. Streisand), 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_360)
- Jenny Romaine and Sukkos Mob; Wayne Barrett on New York City's Bloomberg/Thompson Mayoral Race; Chris Toensing on Revelations Regarding Marc Garlasco, 2009-10-04 (Box 20, Item 718_0869)
- Jenny Romaine and the Sukkos Mob; Wayne Barrett on Bloomberg and the Mayoral Election; Chris Toensing on Human Rights Watch and Marc Garlasco, 2009-10-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_342)
- Sara Miller Llano on Hugo Chavez's Anti-Semitism and Anti-Semitism in Latin America; Kiera Feldman on Jewish Seniors and Health Care Reform; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Madoff, 2009-10-11 (Box 20, Item 718_0891)
- Kiera Feldman on Workmen's Circle; Sheila Krumholz on Health Care Lobby Money, 2009-10-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_307)
- Sara Miller Llano on Anti-Semitism (in Los Angeles, Venezuela); Kiera Feldman on Workmen's Circle; Sheila Krumholz on Health Care Lobby Money; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Madoff, 2009-10-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_343)
- Sophie Tucker Special with Jody Rosen, Lloyd Ecker, and Richard Martin, 2009-10-18 (Box 20, Item 718_0890)
- Sophie Tucker Marathon: Lloyd Ecker, 2009-10-18 (Box 20, Item 718_0896)
- Sophie Tucker Marathon: Jody Rosen, 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_288)
- Sophie Tucker Marathon: Lloyd Ecker, 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_289)
- Sophie Tucker, "My Yiddishe Momme," "The Man I Love", 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_290)
- Sophie Tucker Marathon: Richard Martin of Archeophone Records, 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_334)
- Sophie Tucker: Lloyd Ecker (Partial), Richard Martin, Part 2, 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_344)
- Sophie Tucker: Jody Rosen; Lloyd Ecker (Beginning), Part 1, 2009-10-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_345)
- Amira Hass at Columbia, 2009-11-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_285)
- Sydney Levy and J.J. Goldberg on J Street Conference; Jeff Sharlet on Stupak-Pitts Amendment; Ethan Heitner on Mets Hebron Fund Benefit, 2009-11-14 (Box 20, Item 718_0878)
- Sydney Levy and J.J. Goldberg on J Street Conference; Jeff Sharlot on Stupak-Pitts House Anti-Abortion Amendments and The Family; Ethan Heitner on Mets Hebron Fund Benefit, 2009-11-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_346)
- Nomi Prins on Financial Regulations; Jonathan Berger on Stuard Sherman Exhibitions, Nothing Up my Sleeve and Beginningless Thought / Endless Seeing; Yoav Shamir on Defamation, 2009-11-22 (Box 20, Item 718_0883)
- Nomi Prins on Financial Reform Legislation; Jonathan Berger on His Exhibitions, Beginningless Thought/Endless Seeing: The Works of Stuart Sherman and Stuart Sherman: Nothing Up My Sleeve; Yoav Shamir on Defamation, 2009-11-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_347)
- Abe Velez Hosts the Music Group Beyond the Pale, 2009-11-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_326)
- Mitchell Plitnick on Settlement Freezes and Jerusalem; Trita Parsi on Iran; Cecilie Surasky on the Silencing of Critics of Israel, 2009-12-06 (Box 20, Item 718_0897)
- Trita Parsi, 2009-12-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_286)
- Mitchell Plitnick on Settlement Freeze and East Jerusalem; Trita Parsi on Iran; Cecilie Surasky of Muzzle Watch, 2009-12-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_348)
- Akiva Eldar on How Americans Fund Pro-Settler Israeli Troops; Jeff Sharlet on Role of The Family on Anti-Gay Legislation in Uganda; Gersh Kuntzman on the Bedford Bike Lane, 2009-12-13 (Box 20, Item 718_0894)
- Akiva Eldar on US Tax Exemptions that Fund Pro-Settler IDF Soldiers; Jeff Sharlet on Christian Right and Uganda's Anti-Gay Bill; Bedford Avenue Bike Lane with Gersh Kuntzman, 2009-12-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_349)
- Shana Liebman and Elliot Kalan on Heeb's Storytelling Series; Hella Winston on Rabbinic Sexual Abuse in the Orthodox Community; Ari Berman on Joe Lieberman and Health Care, 2009-12-20 (Box 20, Item 718_0887)
- Shana Liebman and Elliot Kalan on Heeb's Storytelling Series; Hella Winston on Rabbinic Sexual Abuse in the Orthodox Community; Ari Berman on Joe Lieberman and Health Care, 2009-12-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_350)
- Max Ajl on Gaza Freedom March; Mark Greif on the Legacy of Irving Kristol, 2009-12-27 (Box 20, Item 718_0868)
- Max Ajl on Gaza Freedom March, 2009-12-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_287)
- Max Ajl on Gaza Freedom March; Mark Greif on Irving Kristol; Dinah Rose on Jewish Free School Case, 2009-12-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_309)
- Hanukkah Songs, 2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_367)
- Gaza One Year Later: Amira Hass in October 2009 on Gaza after Invasion, Helena Cobban Interview, Dr. Nancy Murray on Impacts of Israeli Violence on Mental Health in Gaza, 2010-01-03 (Box 20, Item 718_0879)
- Helena Cobban Interview, 2010-01-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_368)
- Israeli Film, Ajami, 2010-01-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_366)
- Gaza One Year Later: Tel Aviv Demonstration, Amira Hass Excerpts from Columbia Talk, Helena Cobban on Egypt, Dr. Nancy Murray on Impacts Violence in Gaza, International Steering Committee Gaza Freedom March, 2010-01-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_414)
- Cecilie Surasky on the Suppression of Dissent on the Israeli Occupation; Scandar Copti and Yaron Shani on Ajami; Alan Levin with Fred Jerome on Einstein, Israel, and Zionism, 2010-01-17 (Box 20, Item 718_0899)
- Alan Levine Interviews Fred Jerome, Author of Einstein on Israel and Zionism, 2010-01-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_363)
- Cecilie Surasky of Muzzle Watch; Directors Yaron Shani and Scandar Copti on Ajami; Alan Levine Interviews Fred Jerome on Einstein on Israel and Zionism: His Provocative Ideas About the Middle East, 2010-01-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_447)
- Helena Cobban on Lebanon; David Zelnick and Jordan Schildcrout on Angels in America; Laila el-Haddad on Gaza Mom, 2010-01-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_415)
- Alisa Solomon with David Lehman on A Fine Romance: Jewish Songwriters, American Songs; Maria LaHood on Samantar vs. Yousef USSC Somali Human Rights Case, 2010-01-24 (Box 20, Item 718_0920)
- Maria LaHood on Samantar v. Yousuf Case; Alisa Solomon Talks with David Lehman about A Fine Romance: Jewish Songwriters, American Songs, 2010-01-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_446)
- Mariah Blake on Texas Textbook Standards; D.D. Guttenplan on American Radical: The Life and Times of I.F. Stone; Donna Nevel on Israeli Hasbara and Israel's Attack on the Goldstone Report During International Holocaust Remembrance Day, 2010-01-31 (Box 20, Item 718_0924)
- Don Guttenplan on American Radical: The Life and Times of I.F. Stone, 2010-01-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_392)
- Mariah Blake on Texas Textbook Standards; Don Guttenplan on American Radical: The Life and Times of I.F. Stone; Donna Nevel on Israeli Hasbara and Israel's Attack on the Goldstone Report During International Holocaust Remembrance Day, 2010-01-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_448)
- Readings from The Great Depression: A Diary, Part 2, 2010-02-07 (Box 20, Item 718_0913)
- The Great Depression: A Diary with James Ledbetter, Part 1, 2010-02-07 (Box 20, Item 718_0914)
- Brian Pickett Readings from The Great Depression: A Diary, 2010-02-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_380)
- The Great Depression: A Diary with Jim Ledbetter, 2010-02-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_397)
- Winter Marathon: James Ledbetter The Great Depression: A Diary and Readings by Brian Pickett, Part 1, 2010-02-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_449)
- Winter Marathon: The Great Depression: A Diary, Part 2, 2010-02-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_451)
- Cecilie Surasky on Developments in Israel's Campaign Against Dissenters; Breaking the Silence Report on Israeli Soldiers' Testimonies; Felix Moeller and Jessica Jacoby on Harlan: In the Shadow of Jew Suss, 2010-03-07 (Box 20, Item 718_0901)
- Harlan - In the Shadow of Jew Süss with Felix Moeller and Jessica Jacoby (Partial), 2010-03-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_373)
- Cecilie Surasky of Muzzle Watch; The Only Democracy? Breaking the Silence Executive Director Dana Golan; Harlan - In the Shadow of Jew Süss with Felix Moeller and Jessica Jacoby, 2010-03-07; cuid34405 (Box 30, Item 718_0919)
- Dana Golan on Breaking the Silence NGO, 2010-03-07; cuid34406 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_398)
- Israel Defense Forces (IDF) March 9 Demonstration; David Biale on "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; Jodi Jacobson on Stupall-Pitts Fallout; Chip Berlet on Return of the Militias, 2010-03-14 (Box 20, Item 718_0919)
- "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; IDF Demonstration; Stupak Ad, 2010-03-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_386)
- March 9 Demonstration at Friends of the IDF Dinner; David Biale on "Size Doesn't Matter" Video; Jodi Jacobson on Stupak Blowback; Chip Berlet on Resurgence of Right-Wing Militias and Populist Rebellion, 2010-03-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_452)
- Dubai Killing of Hamas Leader Mahmoud al-Mabhouh, Al-Jazeera Report on Reaction in Israel (Excerpts), 2010-03-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_396)
- Josh Blumenthal on Lawfare Conference with Josh Nathan-Kazis; Alan Levine on Debbie Almontaser Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Ruling; Ayman Mohyeldin on Dubai Killing, 2010-03-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_453)
- Steve Krubiner on J Street and Knesset Investigation; Christian Parenti on Nuclear Catastrophe in Japan; Jeff Sharlet on C Street: The Fundamentalist Threat to American Democracy, 2010-03-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_406)
- Alisa Solomon on Passover Music; Hanna Siniora on Simon Wiesenthal Center's Plans for a Museum of Tolerance on the Mamilla Cemetery Site in Jerusalem; Lois Uttley on Women and Health Care Bill; Joan Marhi on Passover Food, 2010-03-28 (Box 20, Item 718_0906)
- Hanna Siniora on the Museum of Tolerance in Mamilla, Jerusalem; Lois Uttley on Health Care Bill; Joan Nathan on Food for Passover, 2010-03-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_455)
- Liz Krueger on the New York State Budget; Jeff Halper on Israeli Efforts to Rewrite International Law; Hasia Diner on We Remember with Reverence and Love, 2010-04-04 (Box 20, Item 718_0917)
- We Remember with Reverence and Love American Jews and the Myth of Silence after the Holocaust, 1945-1962, 2010-04-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_374)
- Hasia Diner on Her Book We Remember with Reverence and Love American Jews and the Myth of Silence after the Holocaust, 1945-1962, 2010-04-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_381)
- Kiera Feldman, Birthright Intro; Jeff Halper, International Law, 2010-04-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_401)
- Liz Krueger on NY State Budget; Jeff Halper on Israel's Efforts to Rewrite International Law; Hasia Diner on the Myth of American Jewish Response to the Holocaust, 2010-04-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_454)
- Birthright Chronicles: "The Bedouin Desert Village Experience," Parts 1 and 2, 2010 April 8; 2010 June 13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_375)
- Cecilie Surasky on Anat Kamm and Divestment; Richard Kim and Frances Fox Piven on Cloward-Piven Controversy; Seth Wessler and Aine Duggan on Welfare, 2010-04-11 (Box 20, Item 718_0916)
- Cecilie Surasky on Berkeley and American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC), Anat Kamm; Richard Kim and Frances Fox Piven on Cloward/Piven Conspiracy; Áine Duggan and Seth Wessler on Poverty, Food Security, and Welfare, 2010-04-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_445)
- AIPAC and Berkeley [2015-010], circa 2010-04-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_603)
- Budrus: Spielman 1, Iltizam Morrar, Spielman 2; Barbara Hogan of South Africa, 2010-04-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_365)
- Ronit Avni on Budrus; Kiera Feldman Reporting on Birthright Chronicles 1; Connie Field on Have You Heard from Johannesburg?, 2010-04-18 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_444)
- Max Blumenthal Demo, 2010-04-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_403)
- Jenny Romaine with David Buchbinder, 2010-04-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_442)
- Petra Bartosiewicz on Syed Fahad Hashmi Case; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Department of Education and Anti-Semitism on Campuses; Max Ajl in Gaza with Updates on Local Conditions, 2010-05-02 (Box 20, Item 718_0902)
- Petra Bartosiewicz on Syed Fahad Hashmi case; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Department of Education and Anti-Semitism on Campuses; Max Ajl Reporting from Gaza, 2010-05-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_443)
- Nadia Hijab on Palestinian Roads; Cecilie Surasky on Developments in Israel's Campaign Against Dissenters; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on Study of the Jewish Mother Image, 2010-05-09 (Box 20, Item 718_0907)
- Nadia Hijab on Palestinian Roads; Cecilie Surasky on Developments in Israel's Campaign Against Dissenters; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Joyce Antler on Study of the Jewish Mother Image, 2010-05-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_441)
- Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa; Huwaida Arraf on Israeli Navy's Confrontation with the Free Gaza Flotilla, 2010-06-06 (Box 20, Item 718_0910)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa, Part 1, 2010-06-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_378)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa, Part 2, 2010-06-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_439)
- Marathon: Sasha Polakow-Suransky on The Unspoken Alliance: Israel's Secret Relationship with Apartheid South Africa; Huwaida Arraf on Gaza Flotilla, Part 2, 2010-06-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_440)
- Kiera Feldman on Birthright Chronicles, Part 2, 2010-06-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_377)
- Cecilie Surasky, Flotilla Fallout, BDS-Israel Divestment; Helen Thomas; Phyllis Bennis; Birthright 2 with Kiera Feldman, 2010-06-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_438)
- Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel, 2010-06-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_402)
- Brad Lander, 2010-06-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_393)
- Brad Lander on NYC/New York State Budget; Richard Silverstein on Israel's Investigation of Flotilla; Pablo Alvarado on Arizona Immigrant Law; Benita Jain of Immigrant Defense Project, 2010-06-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_430)
- 6/5/2010 Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel: Donna Nevel, Esther Kaplan, Hannah Mermelstein, Kathleen Peratis, Yonatan Shapira, and J.J. Goldberg, 2010-07-04 (Box 20, Item 718_0909)
- 6/5/2010 Boycott, Divestment, Sanctions (BDS) Panel: Donna Nevel, Esther Kaplan, Hannah Mermelstein, Kathleen Peratis, Yonatan Shapira, and J.J. Goldberg, 2010-07-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_431)
- Netanyahu Demonstration; Song From the River to the Sea; Chants; Song Keep on Walkin', 2010-07-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_400)
- M.J. Rosenberg on Netanyahu/Obama Washington Meeting; Jeffrey Edelstein on the YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews of Eastern Europe; Rabbi Alissa Wise and Jenny Romaine on Ma'yan and the It's Not Fair! Production, 2010-07-11 (Box 20, Item 718_0915)
- Rabbi Alissa Wise, Shoshi Shapiro, and Carolyn Kettig on Theatrical Production, That's Not Fair, 2010-07-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_382)
- The YIVO Encyclopedia of Jews in Eastern Europe; Klezmer Dance Tune "Skotshne" from An-ski Ethnographic Expedition; Song from Yiddish Operetta Shulamis; Avrom Goldfadn; Children's Chorus, 2010-07-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_399)